Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 19 August 2022

Website Privacy Policy
======================

Thank you for choosing to part of the community at [https://chloeting.com](https://chloeting.com/) (the "Website") by Chloe Ting ("Company," "we," "us," or "our"). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy.

This Privacy Policy notice serves to inform you of the information we collect about you, why we need to collect this data, how we use it and your rights in relation to it, and applies when you use our Website or engage with us in other related ways — including any email marketing or information shared with us through our Discord server, found at discord.gg/chloeting ("Services"). By continuing to use the Website and its Services you consent to the contents of this Privacy Policy. As such, please ensure you read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our commitment to you. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@chloeting.com](mailto:support@chloeting.com).

### Information We Collect

### How We Use Your Information

### Sharing Your Information

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

### How We Handle Your Social Logins

### Third-Party Websites

### How Long We Keep Your Information

### How We Keep Your Information Safe

### Your Privacy Rights

### Controls for Do-Not-Track Features

### Privacy Rights for California Residents

### Notice Updates

### Contact Us

### Reviewing, Updating or Deleting Your Data

###### © 2024 Chloe Ting

###### Support

###### Socials
